

# Abdul Hannan

Computer Engineer

- +8801952677195
- Mannanbabor95@gmail.com
- Lakshmipur /Chittagong/BD
- Github-/AbdulHannanBabor
- linkedin-/in/abdul-hannan-43629b1b0/

## ABOUT ME

The Last few years I have spent most of my time doing front end developer and web development. Last 1 years I made Some projects using HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP5.1. And I also learned JavaScript. Mainly my focus is web development. I want to see myself as a full-stack developer in near future.

I believe I am a fast learner. Now I want to use my whole skill to do something real world. That's why I am seeking a job that will allow me to gain experience and measure my performance.

# SKILLS

#### 7/10

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap & Front-End Framework

#### 9/10

Project Management & Analytical

#### 6/10

Back-end, Database, Git, Linux, Figma

#### 10 / 10

Interpersonal skills

#### 6 / 10

JavaScript & problem-solving

# EDUCATION

3.26/ B.SC in Computer Science & Engineering Eastern University 2017-2021

#### 3.00/HSC

Lakshmipur Govt College 2013-2014

## 4.69/SSC

Shamgonj High School 2008-2012

# EXPERIENCE

## Full Stack Web Developer

Programing Hero/Dhaka/01/08/2021-15/11/2021

This course helped me to become a full-stack web developer. I think in the near future I will be able to improve my skills.

- HTML,CSS,Bootstrap
- JavaScript, Back-end and Database
- Git and Figma and Website Analytics

### ITEE Training

Eastern University CSE Department /Savar/05/03/20-10/06/2020

Because of this training, I think I am filled with knowledge of international standard computer science.

- Project Management and leadership skills
- Program Organizing and English communication skill

Basic Computer Skills Training Global I. T/ Lakshmipur/01/03/2015 - 06/06/2015

Through this course I got acquainted with computer for the first time in my life. Through this course I gained skills Data entry & analytics, information analysis, Operating Systems, Customer Service, Article Writing and Graphic Design.

- MS Office
- presentation skill
- Fast Typing

References: Professor Dr. Md. Mahfuzur Rahman, Dean, Chairperson and Professor Eastern University, Email: <a href="mailto:dean-et@easternuni.edu.bd">dean-et@easternuni.edu.bd</a>